# **ALEIA JACOBS**

Cell: 503-530-6068 aljacobs@chapman.edu

_

Passionate film student bringing experience from editing ten Chapman University student films and spending over 700 hours on sets. Dedicated to working with the key crew to support their creative visions. Efficient and self-motivated with an aptitude for managing strict deadlines and multi-tasking.

RECENT WORK SAMPLES: https://tinyurl.com/LuzShortFilm https://tinyurl.com/MyHouseFilm

#### **SKILLS**

- Advanced in Avid Media Composer, Adobe Premiere, and Adobe Photoshop
- Proficient in After Effects, Davinci Resolve, Protools, Microsoft Office, and photography

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS**: FILM PRODUCTION - EDITING

Expected in 05/2022

Chapman University, Orange, CA

- 4.0 GPA
- Minor in Visual Journalism
- Dean's List, Presidential Scholarship Recipient

# University of Cape Town, Cape Town, South Africa

01/2020 - 06/2020

- Semester Study Abroad
- Faculty of Humanities

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# TINTOY PRODUCTIONS

Cape Town, South Africa

# **Production Intern**

02/2020 to Present

- Assisted with administrative support
- Aided in post production workflow and provided assistance on set
- Learned the entire workflow from pre to post production of a boutique production company

# HANDEL'S HOMEMADE ICE CREAM & YOGURT

Sherwood, OR

# **Shift Manager**

06/2017 to 01/2020

- Trained and supervised the actions of up to six staff members at one time
- Performed closing duties with the till such as counting money, depositing earnings, and transcribing records
- Served customers and produced pre-packaged products to sell

# STUDENT FILM PROJECTS

How to Kill a Cowboy (2019-Present) - Editor

Gnarly (2019-Present) - Editor

My House (2019) - Editor, Digital Imaging Technician, and Script Supervisor

Luz (2019) - Writer, Director, and Editor

Foundation (2019) - 2nd Assistant Director

Waldo the Plumber (2019) - Editor, Production Designer, and Script Supervisor

Boiling Point (2019) - First Assistant Director, Editor, and Digital Imaging Technician

Room for Rent (2019) - Three Episode Short Form Series - Editor and Sound Designer

• Official selection for LA Shorts International Film Festival

Phantom Blonde (2019) - Editor and Script Supervisor

Assembly Required (2019) - First Assistant Camera and Second Assistant Camera

Home for the Summer (2018) - Best Boy Electric

Bloom (2018) - Best Boy Grip